brewdog.com 2019-04-01

# Cookie and Privacy Policy - Customer Services - BrewDog

**Privacy Policy**

At BrewDog, we are committed to maintaining strong and meaningful privacy protections for customers. Our privacy policy is designed to inform you about the information we collect, how we use it, and your options about certain uses of information. 

This privacy policy sets out how BrewDog PLC collect and process information about you. We gather your information when, among other things, you visit our website, apply for shares, use our applications on mobile phones, apply for a job, access our social media experiences, use your discount card in our bars or when you take part in our other experiences where this Policy is posted. By participating in these, you consent to your information being collected, processed/or and shared in accordance with this Policy.

Below is summarised the key points from our Privacy Policy which can be read in full [HERE](https://www.brewdog.com/customer-services/privacy-policy).

**What information do we collect and why?**

We collect and use information when you interact with us, when you use our products and services, and when you visit our websites. This information is used to: Deliver and provide products or services; establish and maintain customer accounts; contact you about our products and services and direct offers or promotions to you; and monitor website statistics. Information may also be aggregated or anonymised by us for business and marketing uses. BrewDog may use your Information for direct marketing purposes, including providing updates, newsletters, events or other communications that we think may interest you.

You may actively give us Information about yourself when you become an Equity Punk, purchase products from our online shop, respond to a customer survey, enter a competition, join our Intergalactic Beer Visa program, email us or post in our forum. The information that you provide may include your name, date of birth, email address, telephone number, delivery address, billing address and password.

Note also that information you disclose in our forum is accessible by anyone, including third parties not bound by this policy.

When you visit one of our websites or use our forum, we may also automatically collect information through the use of various technologies, including through "cookies", which is explained HERE.

**What choices do I have?**

You have a choice to remove your personal information by accessing your account and deleting your information even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of offers such as your free birthday beer, referral perks or other BrewDog offerings.

If you are a shareholder we have a legal obligation to let you know about certain updates, we therefore restrict amendment of certain fields to allow us to meet that obligation. However if you have a question, concern or complaint about this you can contact us at privacy@brewdog.com.

You have full control over how we communicate with you and can change your preferences through your BrewDog.com account.

We’ve also made it super simple to select the marketing you receive by accessing your marketing preferences with a link to a personalized preference center at the bottom of every email.

**How can I access and control my personal information?**

We respect your right to access, correct, request deletion or request restriction of our usage of your personal information as required by applicable UK law. We also take steps to ensure that the personal information we collect is accurate and up to date.

You can see, review and change most of your personal information by signing in to your BrewDog.com account. Please, update your personal information immediately if it changes or is inaccurate.

**How will you share my personal Information?**

We may share your information with our BrewDog entities and affiliates and the third parties described in our privacy policy. We may also share your information with third parties when it is necessary to involve a third party service provider to facilitate or offer our services such as participating in a trading platform, delivering your orders, booking tickets for events or participating on our forum.

We will never share your personal information with a third party that is not directly related to us delivering on our obligation to you or to let you know about cool BrewDog things!

How long will you hold my personal information?

We will not hold onto your personal data longer than necessary to fulfil our commitment to you as a customer or a shareholder.  Personal data processed for any purpose will not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose.

After it is no longer necessary for us to retain your personal information, we will dispose of it in a secure manner according to our data retention and deletion policies.

**Questions about this Policy**

If you have a question, concern or complaint about this Policy or our handling of your information, you can contact us at [privacy@brewdog.com](mailto:privacy@brewdog.com).
